<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Hugo website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring a new data set</title>
      <link>/2020/07/03/exploring-a-new-data-set/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/07/03/exploring-a-new-data-set/</guid>
      <description>Beyond the classic functions like summary(), or str() , there is a set of dedicated packages to explore a new dataset. In this post, I will describe three useful packages which give a good perspective on a new dataset. The first one is visdat which gives tools to visualise at one glance a new dataset.
Its major functions are vis_dat,vis_miss and ,vis_cor vis_dat takes litteraly “looking at the data”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips to produce graphics</title>
      <link>/2020/05/21/graph-in-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/05/21/graph-in-r/</guid>
      <description>Nice and constructive graphics play an important role when it comes to conveying a message.
I personnaly use R with ggplot2, a graphic package. the main advantages of ggplot is that is come with a grammar, a series of rules which once learn, make it very easy to create new plots. Thus I recommend to learn ggplot when starting to use R. It is time consuming at first and the curve is steep but it is totally worth in the long term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a researcher in applied mathematics working at the university of Exeter. I am interested by the use of statistic and machine learning to improve clinical practice. I am currently working on the prediction of Type 1 diabetes thanks to JDRF sponsoring and my aim is to develop tools to identify children who are likely to develop type 1 diabetes and give them an adequate follow up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>